{
    "subject": "resource/David_Thwaites_(flying_ace)",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/nick",
    "object": "Frank",
    "human_readable": "The nickname of David Thwaites (flying ace) is Frank.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9655800461769104,
            "question": "Is David Thwaites also known as Frank?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.943533718585968,
            "question": "Is there a connection between David Thwaites and the nickname 'Frank'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9064376354217529,
            "question": "What does the name 'Frank' represent for David Thwaites?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9005582928657532,
            "question": "What was David Thwaites' nickname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8581650257110596,
            "question": "Can you tell me about David Thwaites' nickname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8294894099235535,
            "question": "What nickname did David Thwaites go by?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7552653551101685,
            "question": "How is Frank related to David Thwaites?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7387558221817017,
            "question": "Who is Frank in relation to David Thwaites?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.732519805431366,
            "question": "Who is known as 'flying ace'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5918884873390198,
            "question": "What is Frank known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The nickname of David Thwaites (flying ace) is Frank.",
            "html": "dbpedia_820_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is known as 'flying ace'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_820_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Frank in relation to David Thwaites?",
            "html": "dbpedia_820_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Frank related to David Thwaites?",
            "html": "dbpedia_820_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_820_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_820_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_820_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_820_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_820_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_820_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_820_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_820_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_820_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_820_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the flying ace's name was David F. Thwaites, but there is no information about his nickname being \"Frank\". The nickname \"Polly\" is mentioned, which refers to his P-47 Thunderbolt aircraft, not a personal nickname for himself."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about David F. Thwaites and his nickname Polly, not Frank. Therefore, the query stating that the flying ace's nickname is Frank does not match the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided to suggest that the nickname of David Thwaites (flying ace) is Frank. Instead, the context discusses his nicknames for his P-47s as \"Polly\" and provides additional facts about his military career and achievements.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of David Thwaites having a nickname \"Frank\" in the provided context.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided about the nickname of David Thwaites being Frank, but rather that he nicknamed his P-47 Thunderbolt \"Polly\".",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context does not mention any nickname for David Thwaites other than \"Polly\" for his P-47 Thunderbolts.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}